

ANDREW KELLEHER

SENIOR MULTIMEDIA DESIGNER & DEV TEAM PROJECT MANAGER

ABOUT

Experienced Senior Multimedia Designer working in the e-learning industry with Cellmedia for the last 18+ years. Skilled in Design, Coding, Interfaces, Interactions and Development. Bachelor of Graphic Design focused in Multimedia from Curtin University. Primarily interested in coding, front and back end development.

SKILLS

- ✓ Adobe Animate
- Adobe Creative Cloud (Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere, After Effects, Audition)
- ✓ Articulate Storyline 360/Rise
- ✓ Adobe Captivate
- / HTML5 / CSS
- JavaScript / jQuery
- ✓ Node.js
- SCORM / LMS
- FFMPEG
- / Jira Helpdesk / Software
- ✓ Team & Project Management
- Client Communication
- Project Planning
- Helpdesk Operation
- Teamwork and Solo Projects

EDUCATION

Lesmurdie High School

1994-1998

Curtin University

BA Arts | Multimedia Design 1998-2001

UWA

Coding Bootcamp 2020-Present

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Cell-media

Senior Multimedia Designer June 2001 - Present

- Lead Interface & Interaction Designer
- Content Planning & Delivery
- · Project Management

Cell-media

MobiliseMe Dev Team Project Manager June 2020 - Present

- Project Manager for Development Team of 4
- Bespoke Onboarding and Contractor Management Portal

CONTACT ME

www.github.com/diemrbond

https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-kelleher-58018588/

mrbondmustdie@gmail.com